-♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D.
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked
at Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now, keep in mind,
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin
or end ♪
♪ La-la-la
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
-Cambot!
-Pan left.
-Gypsy!
-Hi, girl.
-Tom Servo!
-What a cool guy.
-Crow!
-What a wisecracker.
-♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-la-la
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax"
♪ For "Mystery Science
Theater 3000" ♪
♪♪
[Indistinct announcement]
[Applause]
-Uh, Cambot, you don't have to
put applause in now, okay?
But you could, uh,
bring it in a little bit.
Go ahead. Come on in.
A little bit more.
That's good, okay.
People of Earth,
my name is Joel,
and I'm marooned in outer space.
-Commercial sign in 15 seconds.
-Um, I'm the subject
of a bizarre
movie-watching experiment,and now I guess, uh, so are you.
I'm expecting a call any secondnow from the two evil scientists
who shot me into space
for no good reason at all.
-Commercial sign in five, four,
three, two...
Commercial side now.
-Uh, stick around, we --
we'll be right back.
-You know what?
One of the really hard things
about being marooned
in outer space is you start to
miss the little things
that you have every day
on Earth, you know,
like rain and snow
and mini marshmallows.
You know, that's why
these vacuum flowers
are important to me.
They're like the only living --
Oh, I'm being called
by my two evil overlords.
-Come in, Joel Might,
my spunky little space-sock.
-Hey, sirs, what's going on?
-It's time for the invention
exchange.
What have you got for us,
skanky boy?
-Yeah,
I got this new thing here.
It's a, um, looks like
an ordinary circular saw,
but it's actually a safety saw.
See, it's a got a little
infrared light that senses
when your appendages or fingers
are near.
It shuts itself automatically.
I'll show you what I mean.
[Saw powering on]
[Saw buzzing]
Ow!
I'm -- I'm just kidding.
It's a trick.
Fake fingers.
-Oh, yes, we knew that.
Uh, well, it's our turn
for our little experimental
house party this week, Joel.
-Okay, say you want to emulate
Reed Richards
from the Fantastic Four,
and you need a longer arm
to reach something
or change the channel.
Just use our limb-lengthener
here.
-Yes, just select
the appropriate limb.
In this case,
Larry has volunteered his arm.
Comfy?
-Meh.
-Yes, all right,
and just stretch away.
-Ow!
[Groans]
Ow.
-Oh, it doesn't hurt that much,
you whiny baby.
-[Groaning]
-Well, I have a feeling
you're probably violating
somebody's basic human rights,
namely Dr. Erhardt's.
-Thank you.
-Well, speaking of violations,
here is a little
cinematic intrusion called
"The Crawling Hand."
-It has a star from
"Gilligan's Island"
and one from "The Big Valley"
and one from the
Hamburger Helper commercial.
-Yes.
-Enjoy.
-Oh, brother.
[Alarm buzzing]
Movie sign!
♪♪
-"The Crawling Hand."
Hey, Joel.
-Hi.
-How'd the scientists
like your deal?
-Okay. They're crazier than
ever, though, you know.
-Yeah.
-They're kind of dick-weeds
aren't they?
-Hmm, you could say that.
♪♪
-This is like
"Love, American Style."
-Hey, Alan Hale,
isn't that the skipper?
-Yeah.
-Little buddy.
-I can see my house from here,
you guys.
-Hey, Joel, did they do these
titles on a typewriter?
-No, that's the Helvetica
constellation we're looking at.
-Oh.
-Stellar.
-Is Artie Shaw in this?
-No, I don't think so.
-Just off camera.
♪♪
-Ooh.
-Scary.
-Ah.
-Do you read me?
Do you read me?
-Like a book.
-Someone please come in.
My god, my god.
-It's Kirk Douglas.
-Any Town, USA.
-Dr. Weitzberg,
contact range officer.
Paging system now secured
for emergency use only.
-Unless you have a note
from your parents.
-46 hours and 20 minutes,
zero seconds.
-Boy, he really needs a smoke.
-Space Operations,
Florida division.
Hold on.
-It's the press.
-Tell them I'm smoking.
-What do we tell them, Steve?
-I'll tell you
what to tell them.
-Tell them I'm smoking.
-Tell them we sent our second
man to the Moon.
Looks like he's not
coming back easy.
Oh, I'm sorry, Donna.
I shouldn't have said that.
-Oops.
-I'm sorry.
Just tell them I'm smoking.
-He's smoking.
-We can release no statement
at this time.
-Oxygen countdown.
-Mr. Curan would like
a countdown
on the oxygen every 15 seconds.
-And an ashtray.
-Two minutes, 30 seconds.
-No contact for nine full hours.
-Golly.
-Get him some decaf.
-Same thing all over again.
-Too many years at
the Strasberg school.
-Same thing all over again.
-Isn't that Nick
from "The Big Valley"?
-Yeah.
-We get the whole rigs clicking
like a dream.
-Two minutes, 15 seconds.
-And 62 bottles of beer
on the wall.
-We licked every problem,
put a man on the Moon,
know we got him off.
Everything worked fine
but Lockhart.
What happened to him?
-Two minutes, zero seconds.
[Telephone buzzes]
-Mr. Curan's desk.
Yes, sir, one moment.
-He's smoking.
-The White House.
-Tell them I'm smoking.
-No, not now.
No.
-No self-respecting scientist
would have his shirt unbuttoned
that far.
-Mr. Curan feels certain
that there's...
no hope for Captain Lockhart.
Yes, sir.
-Unless he's smoking.
-Isn't that a David Bowie song?
-I hate cappuccino.
-One minute, 30 seconds.
-Hey,
scientists shouldn't litter.
-You all right?
-Shut up and throw the cup away.
-One minute, 15 seconds.
-How's our boss holding up?
-He's probably smoking.
-Barrenger?
Well, as usual,
he's not said a word,
but I wouldn't get too close
to him if I were you.
-Yeah, his breath could stop
a Titan missile.
-I was figuring on giving him
a sedative.
-Funny.
-Hey, they all got stripes
in their hair.
-Yeah, it looks like
Land of the Skunk People.
-Who is it?-Hairstyles by Gordon of Gotham.
-Will be in about 60 seconds.
Well, we've done it
your way twice.
-Well, now, we don't pretend to
know all the answers.
-Apparently, no one does.
-Except for her.
-For every frontier
there's been explorers,
men have died.
We've only lost two men on
the strangest frontier of all.
-Cable.
-There are millions of people
in this world, Dr. Weitzberg,
but there are only four men leftwho can handle the lunar rocket.
-The Beatles?
-And her.
-We've lost one-third
of the men we have.
It's like a conveyor to --
to oblivion.
-Like your career.
-30 seconds.
-The situation that happened to
those first two men
was not only duplicated,
but widely exaggerated
in their training.
-Those men did not have
a mental crack-up.
I'd stake my life on it.
-There is no duplicate
for the solitude of space.
If those men could've looked
in their viewing screen
and seen two, three,
or more sister ships
alongside out there,
they wouldn't have panicked.
-Bang.
-Ow.
-Those men did not panic.
-Why are they shouting?
-...nine, eight...
-The remaining four men...
-Seven seconds till
he slaps table.
-Then do it without me.
-Four, three, two, one.
-Zero.
Oxygen depleted.
-Slap table.
-[Slaps table]
-Thank you.
-[Fake crying]
-I'll see you in Washington
tomorrow.
-I'm going to get some air.
-Hey, she's making that loon
call with her hands.
-[Whistles]
-Cool.
-Steve, did you ever think aboutgetting your hair frosted?
-Steve...
-I know you don't have
a widow's peak now.
-...did he knew about
Donna and Mel Lockhart?
-I don't know, Doc.
If he did, I doubt it would makemuch difference.
-Let's see,
you mess with this switch,
twist that, flip this...
Oh, someone's coming.
Good luck with that.
-[Laughs]
-Well, Steve, we might as well
write off four more men.
-I can't take much more of this,Doc.
-Yeah, soon I'll have to move
off the corner of this Formica.
-I don't know
how he can justify it.
-Well, our boss is
Secretary of Space Operations,
and that cabinet post's
entitled him
to be a very daring man.
-No, we got to stop him, Doc.
-All right, Steve,
before you go see him tomorrow,
stop by my office.
-I'll give you a protein rinse.
-I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
The pattern,
it's the same as before --
perfect takeoff, clear contact
all the way, perfect landing.
You heard Lockhart when he was
on the lunar surface.
Liftoff from the Moon, perfect.
One hour later, nothing,
and we had him right here, Doc.
-Sure wish I had that command ofmy arms.
-If he wanted to talk to us,
he didn't even have to push
a lousy button.
-Look at that fluid motion.
-Do you read me?
-Lockhart.
-Huh?
-X-20 approaching ionosphere.
-Hey, someone screwed up
all the knobs.
-Someone please come in.
Oh, my God.
-Max Headroom's dad.
[Static buzzing]
And the music goes round
and round it comes out here.
-Hey, it's a spirograph.
-X-20 to Moon Blast,
do you read me?
-Lockhart, this is Moon Blast.
Curan, Steve Curan.
Come in, X-20.
-Steve.
-Look, it's Tammy Faye Bakker.
-It's coming on again.
-Yeah, it looks more like
Robert Smith from The Cure.
-My god, my god.
Kill, kill.
-Looks like he needs the cure.
-What's wrong with that man?
-I don't know, Steve.
This is Doc Weitzberg.
How long have you been
without oxygen?
-15, maybe 20 minutes.
-That's impossible.
-Why did you break contact?
-Let me contact, please.
Kill.
No, no! No, don't!
Steve, I-I-I can't make it.
Lost control.
-Have you considered
frosting your hair?
-Push the red.
-I can't push that red button.
It'll blow him up.
-Push the red button.
-I can't make it.
-I think he's taking acting
lessons from William Shatner.
-No, no,
something makes my arm move,
makes me do things, kill, kill.
-This is Major Tom
to ground control.
-I'm 200,000 feet.
Push the red.
There's something in me.
-Why do you want us to push it?
-You can push it if you want to.
-It's better when you push it.
-I can't move my arm.
Kill, kill.
-Looks like the Dow's
up about three points.
-Push the red.
No more time.
-What's his position?
Where is he?
-Inland.
Populated area, California.
-140,000.
Push the red.
-Must push button.
-Oh, my god, my god.
Doc, Steve, help me.
Help me.
-Well, he still has good teeth.
-Push the red.
-Here, I'll push it.
Let me be the one.
I want to push this thing.
-7,000!
-Nope.
-Push it.
-Push that.
-Push that
and he's an astro-not.
[Explosion]
-God, my god.
Doc, Steve, help me.
Help me.
Push the red.
70,000.
-Sounds like my old phy-ed
teacher.
"Push it. Push it."
[Explosion]
-And then the tape ran out.
But we've got it on CD, too.
-Well, that's one tape we don't
want Donna to transcribe.
-Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
-It's pretty morbid to keep
listening to that.
-How can a man
continue to function
without oxygen for 20 minutes?
-Can't.
-Lockhart did, so we know
something kept him functioning.
-A substitute for oxygen?
-New oxygen lite.
-I don't know, Steve,
and ever since we lost Nelson,
an idea has been
buzzing around in my brain
like a fly,
a very persistent fly.
-[Imitates fly buzzing]
-After hearing Lockhart,
the buzzing stopped.
You know, I think I've hit
on something.
Want to hear it out with me?
-Go ahead. Have at it.
-Well, I think what kept
Lockhart going was life,
an independent vital force,
something living.
-Oh, and I suppose
next you'll tell me
there's rings around Uranus.
-Well, living covers a lot
of territory, Steve,
and I don't think
Lockhart was alone
on his return flight
any more than Nelson was.
-Oh, now.
-I'm not talking about
little green men.
As a matter of fact,
I may not talk at all
unless I get some encouragement.
-Well, what do you need, uh,
a drink maybe?
-What, are you coming onto me?
-...and you're the one
that can get Barrenger
to give it to me.
-Time, for what?
-Time to prove that this force,
this new life,
was born on the X-20.
-Go ahead.
-I need you with me
all the way, Steve.
-He asked me. He asked me.
-I am with you.
[Sighs]
-What makes life?
A certain particular combination
of molecules or carbon
or silicons or nitrogen
or any number
of these things...
-Blah, blah, blah.
-A certain temperature,
mix well.
Call it what you will.
-Serve over cracked ice
and garnish with a parasol.
-...swirling together
in tiny orbits
fuses these things into
a precise energy relationship
which we call life.
-Now, wait a minute.
What you're saying is that,
uh, in certain...
-Boy, he's slow, huh?
-...life might mutate
or even fully evolve
in a matter of hours
or even minutes?
-Uh, no, you're wrong.
-Well, what happens when
we send a man up there?
-Speed it up. Let's go.
-You see, we don't send
just a man in a rocket.
We send up living cells...
-Hey, down in front.
-Oh, snap out of it.
-Hey.
-...bacteria, germs.
We throw in radioactivity.
We introduce all these
to cosmic rays.
Do we upset this balance?
Do we start a cycle?
Does a living cell from Earth
romance a cosmic ray
and give birth
to an illegitimate monster
who makes his nest in...
-I wonder if there's
an abridged
version of this movie.
-Beginning to add up, isn't it?
-Perhaps it...
-If there is, let's burn it.
-...be dying.
Anything evolving
so rapidly could...
-Never burn your abridges.
-Well, Steve?
-Quite a chunk.
-Throw out the logic pills
when you swallow it.
This theory can't be measured
by anything we already know.
-Doo, doo, doo, doo.
-Sounds like a good case.
-I was hoping you'd say that.
-Barrenger won't.
He won't go for a theory,
even if it's true.
-Well, then lie to him,
but buy me the time.
-Buy me things.
Buy me things.
-All right.
-No dancing, no dancing,
not allowed.
No dancing, no dancing,
-What a grouch.
-It's just like "Footloose."
-No rats, not allowed.
-Unless they're on the menu.
-No acting, not allowed.
-And you're going to be
a nurse, Patsy?
-Well, what're you doing
with them?
-I picked them up at
the express office for grandpa.
They're for the lab at school.
-Well, maybe your grandfather's
a biology professor,
and your boyfriend
is a pre-med student,
but my father is the sheriff,
and rats and the law don't mix.
-I thought they were
synonymous.
-Voilà, no rats.
-Good trick.
-You didn't bite.
-Hmm?
-When I said boyfriend.
-You mean Paul?
-Oh, then he isn't just
a mutual interest
in hives and chicken pox.
-He's very nice.
-But how did you hook him?
-Rubber frog and pork rind?
-The Lone Wolf, they call him.
-[Howls]
-Oh, I'm not saying
you're not stacked,
but he's just not with it.
-Just good friends.
-Joel, move your head.
Thank you.
-Hey, he looks like Bub
from "My Three Sons."
-You think I'm kidding, huh?
Didn't you see that thing
last night?
-What, you mean "My Three Sons"?
-I didn't see anything.
-Well, I phoned your father.
Why, there was a fireball
in the sky as big as a house.
He didn't see it, either.
-Well, what do you
think it was?
-Didn't I tell you?
Eat, drink, and be merry.
Tomorrow, you die.
-Well, no, wouldn't it be today
if there was
a fireball last night?
-Gloomy Gus.
Hey, he's got a woody.
[Chuckling]
-The traffic commission
has decided --
[Radio shuts off]
-Hi.
-Hi, Paul.
-Come on, sit down beside me.
-Nah, I'll sit where
the rat was.
-Come on, finish them up.
Let's get going.
-Can we stop by my house?
-What for?
It's getting late.
-I've got to pick up
my bathing suit.
-But I told you
I'd meet you here.
You said you'd have
your suit with you.
-Mr. Charm.
-I just can't get used to going
swimming at Christmastime.
-With a suit on?
-Well, I can tell you
one thing.
-What's that?
-It's for real.
You sound like a married
couple already.
-[Laughs]
You.
-That's not milk.
That's pancake batter
she's drinking.
-All right.
-Pancake batter?
You're soaking in it.
-Shotgun.
-Okay.
I got to drop these at home
for grandpa anyhow.
-Okay, let's get move on.
-Hey, they packed a lunch.
-Bye, Patsy.
-Goodbye, you two lovebirds.
-Ratatouille.
-Hey, Paul, what did they say
to you over at the school
about that thing
in the sky last night?
-Nothing, why?
Everybody said it was a meteor.
-[Scoffs]
-Hey, come on.
Don't tell me you're still
scared of them flying saucers.
-Come on, Bub.
You can't let fear
run your life.
-Yeah, pops.
-Eat, drink, and be merry.
-Get over it.
-Yeah, take a lesson
from these teeners.
Twist your troubles away.
-♪ He's got the latest groove,
and it's real clean ♪
-♪ Have you heard
-Let's twist again
like we did last summer, Joel.
-Yeah.
-♪ Don't you
[Tires screech]
-Yowza.
-Look, it's Ed Begley Sr.
-Oh, look at you.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Picked it up for you
at the express office.
-Thank you.
-I love you, Grandpa.
Got to run.
-Hello there, Mr. Farnstrom.
-I never will understand
how you do it.
-It's easy, I just tie
the sleeves around my neck.
-It's 15 minutes
past the last bell,
and already you are offsomewhere with my granddaughter.
-Well, we have a system, sir,
a secret system.
-A secret.
-He looks like a cross between
Jerry Mathers and James Dean.
-"Beaver Without a Cause."
-...have to share,
to work together.
-Oh, we got to get out of here.
-Okay.
-Carry me.
-Not me, professor.
When I make it, I'll make it
on my own, all the way.
-Oh, sorry.
-I'm coming.
-What did I tell you?
♪♪
[Bowling pins clatter]
-Hey, baby split.
Wow, that's gonna be
tough to beat.
-Here we are
in the fifth frame.
Crow is staring at
a nasty 6-10 split.
He really needs this one.
-Oh, good hook, yes.
[Bowling pins clatter]
-Oh.
-All right. Great shot.
-Nice shot, Crow, very nice.
-Hey, that puts me over 120,
Joel.
-All right. That was excellent.
-Oh, great game, yeah.
-These new arms
are working great.
-You know, but I hate
these rentals shoes
'cause no matter how much
of that they spray into them,
your feet still smell funny.
-Smell? I didn't know
that you could smell?
-Shh, shh.
-Uh, I'm, uh --
Did I say smell?
Uh, I meant spectral analysis,
of course.
-Hey, I was thinking
let's play murder ball now.
What do you say?
-Uh, no.
-Wait a minute, uh,
I created you guys.
When I say we play murder ball,
we play murder ball.
-Okay, not it.
-Not it.
-Let's do it over.
-Uh, well, how about rock,
paper, scissors, huh?
-Oh, no way, I'm not playing
that with you again.
Look at my hands, look, see.
You know, every time we play,
uh, I got to be scissors,
and you pick rock all the time.
-Hey, it's just the luck
of the draw, Crow.
Come on.
-Mm.
-Okay, Joel,
you win everything.
-Yeah, bye. See ya.
-See ya later, Joel.
-Let's...
Hey, uh, go home
to your mom, yeah.
We're your friends.
-Not.
-Come on, let's ditch him.
-Oh, that's great.
I get it, yeah, yeah.
Thanks, Joel.
Thanks for emptying my load pan.
Thanks for creating us, Joel.
Thanks for making us
intrinsically human, Joel.
Hey, Cambot,
come in a little bit.
Cambot, I want you
to remind of something.
Next time I make a robot,
no more free will.
That's it.
Well, we got commercial.
I hate this.
♪♪
-Ow, ouch, oof, pain.
-Oh, oh, hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, thud.
-Ah.
-[Laughs] Are you hurt?
-Uh, only my pride.
-And my lumbar.
-He landed on it.
-Poor boy, the sensitive
male ego, so easily wounded.
-I think I know now the secret
of how to be successful
with a woman.
-You do?
Tell me.
-You have to be weak, pathetic.
Then they feel sorry for you.
-You're all those things
and less.
-I think you discovered it.
-I know I have.
I always wondered why
some spindly little runts
had the girls chasing after them
because they felt sorry
for them.
-Of course.
-And usually they
have money, too.
-But you were fooling me.
You're not weak.
-Darn right, now I've got you.
-Hey, is this
"From Here to Eternity"?
-No, it just seems
like an eternity.
-Oh, Paul, I guess I'm not
like those other women.
I don't like weak mean at all.
-Listen, will you once and for
all give me a serious answer?
-What about?
-Are you going home to Sweden
after the semester is over?
-Why not?
I only planned to come
to California for a year
to see grandfather and go to
an American school for a while.
-Meet some football teams.
-Nothing has come up
to change my plans.
-What do you mean?
What about me?
-No, I planned there
would be a boy, too.
-Oh.
-Why, you...
-You little minx.
-Oh, no, don't throw my shorts
in the sand.
Damn you.
-Ha-ha.
-All right.
She's a stripping minx.
-Don't come any closer.
I've nothing on.
-Ah, faker, you haven't
had time to undress.
-Maybe I didn't.
-How would he know?
-But I have now.
-Okay, you win.
-I'll accept that.
-Soon-to-be naked is better
than not naked at all.
-You know, I don't think your
grandfather approves of me.
-Because you're naked?
-You're wrong.
He considers you
the best student in his class.
-No, I meant as a member
of the family.
-What do I have to do,
say it in Swedish?
-How do you say moon
in Swedish?
-Hubba-hubba.
-Paul, what does it mean,
"I'm stacked,
and you're not with it."
-Stacked?
-Stacked means
you're really smart.
-Patsy, this afternoon.
-Hey, why is wearing a swimsuit
with a codpiece?
-Oh, just for the halibut.
-Is something wrong?
-Sorry.
-Stop it, you're
giving me a haddock.
-Oh, ho, ho.
-You're a pain in the bass.
-You have no sole.
-Oh.
-Um, how do you
say it in Swedish?
-Say what?
-Nothing. Let's hit the water.
-You know something?
American men marry
much too young.
-You know something?
It's because of Swedish girls
like you.
-The kind that get naked
in public.
-Hey, last one in the fjord's
a rotten egg.
-Hey, it's a beach thermometer.
-But, Donna,
I've called everywhere and
haven't been able to find him.
Didn't he say
where he was going?
-No, he was quite upset
when he left.
He banged on the typewriter
for a while.
He was in a mood.
-I've got to talk to him
right away.
It's urgent.
-I need more calendars.
-...he wants to be alone.
-Well, this is the one time
he shouldn't be alone.
-Doc, you've got me worried.
-I didn't mean to scare you.
This is a matter
of the gravest importance.
-I'll try.
-I'll be in here until I hear
from you,
and, Donna,
everything all right?
-Well, my collar is too tight.
-Yes, Doc.
-Good. Bye.
-Goodbye.
-Boy, they're good swimmers.
-Waders.
See, the sand is hot.
-Boy, that water was cold.
-You know what that means.
[Chuckles]
-All right. Now...
-The biking, then the marathon.
-Now, what?
-The answer.
-Answer?
-Let's have it.
-What answer?
-Take it easy.
-Sorry.
-Are you going to stay here?
-Well, why should I do that?
-So I can marry you, stupid.
-Marry me?
-I'll marry you stupid,
smart, any way.
[Laughs]
-Oh, he upended her.
-Hi, I'm Tom Servo.
-[Screams]
-Hey, I found my watch.
-[Screaming]
Paul take me away, please.
-Sure, baby. Sure.
♪♪
-Did he just offer his hand
in marriage?
-Marta, let me go back for it.
-Well, not exactly his hand.
-I'll lock it in the trunk
of the car.
-No! No!
I couldn't stand it.
Let's go right to the sheriff.
There's been a murder!
-No, not a murder.
-A human hand not a murder?
-Listen, please.
You've just got to trust me.
If it's what I think it is,
it could be
very important for me.
Please.
-Oh, no.
Just take me away from it.
-I love her,
but I want the hand.
I still love her, though,
and that hand
would be really great,
but I don't know what -- Oh.
-Babe, hand, babe, hand.
♪♪
-Put your hands up,
or I'll shoot.
-Mrs. Hotchkiss, it's only me.
-It's Harriet Nelson's
evil twin.
-Paul, what are you doing here?
You said you wouldn't
be home until late.
-Oh, I just remembered
this old pile of papers,
and I thought I'd come back
and look something up.
-Well, what'd you come
in the back door for?
You know how jumpy I am
about noises in the house.
I got Mr. Hotchkiss'
old gun out.
I thought they'd carry a burglarout of here tonight.
-I'm sorry.
-Could I just take
one practice shot at you?
I was kind of psyched.
-I was going to shoot
and ask questions later.
-Just one shot?
-I've got a hair trigger, too.
Well, as long as it's you,
it's okay.
How about some supper?
-Oh, no, thanks. I...
-I have some stew leftover
from last night.
I could heat it up for you.
-No, I found what I was...
-If the gun doesn't kill him,
the stew will.
-I'm not hungry really.
I guess I'll just go up
to my room, if you don't mind.
Thank you.
-Goodnight.
-Hey, come on, one shot.
I'll just wing you.
It won't hurt that much.
-I've got to have that hand.
Can't eat. Can't sleep.
All I do is think about it.
Maybe if there's something --
Oh, no.
-Man, with an extra hand
around the house,
just think of the stuff
I could do.
Just think.
-Hmm.
-Star light, star bright,
first hand I see tonight.
-[Chuckles]
-I wish I may, I wish I might.
-Little human hand, come here.
Little human hand, come on.
Little human hand, yes.
-If you want to catch
a human hand,
you got to think
like a human hand.
♪♪
-That's giant.
That hand's unbelievably huge.
-It's called foreshortening,
Joel.
-Coochy, coochy, coo.
Coochy, coochy, coo.
[Chuckles]
-You've got to hand it to him.
-Went out on a limb
with that one.
-Oh.
-It's a good thing he brought
that freezer wrap along.
-I don't think
it's freezer wrap.
I think it's a handbag.
-Oh!
-[Laughs]
♪♪
-Oh, that'll go great with
a little glass of milk later --
a little honey-cured hand.
Next to the hand cream
on the shelf.
-Yes, Steve.
It's positive.
There is a reading.
-Yes, you've proved
that they are rats.
-I said there was
a positive reading.
This may be all the evidence
we need to convince Barrenger.
-Oh, really?
-Oh, these two guys.
We're in for some serious
acting now.
-Don't you understand
I'm giving you the --
-It's too late, Doc.
-What's that?
-It's my resignation.
-Oh, you talked to him?
-Oh, no, not quite.
He talked.
He said either get in his wagon
or get out.
Well, I'm getting out.
-Well, now, wait a minute.
Tear it up.
You don't need it.
This is the gauge
I've been telling you about.
It measures the results
of cosmic rays
or the presence
of something associated --
-What is the something, Doc?!
-Well, I don't know...
-It's a something.
-...though, I did make
a very important discovery
about Elmer.
-Has he got it?
-Oh --
-Well, how did he get it?
-Probably at a nightclub.
-Oh, I see.
You're not aware of Elmer.
He's a very distinguished rat.
-Perhaps you're familiar
with his glue.
-He was a passenger
on our last space program
before we launched
our first manned rocket.
In the beginning, we thought
he was completely unaffected.
-But he wasn't.
-I think the doctor has been
spending a little too much time
in the rat lab.
-I don't know when he'll turnon the other rats and kill them.
Now, he can unlock
an ordinary cage.
That's why I had
that padlock put on there.
Everyone else around hereseems to think that what he does
is in the range
of an exceptionalrat's capabilities, but I don't.
I think Elmer has thoughts.
-Naughty thoughts.
-Human thoughts.
-Like a human?
-Better than human thoughts.
-Like the something,
the same something
that was in our pilots.
-Well, Steve,
there's a possibility.
♪♪
[Bottles rattling]
[Glass shatters]
-W.C. Handy.
[Dog barking in distance]
-Hey, she's wearing
a drool pad.
-And she's putting on
Dr. Spock's housecoat.
-Doctor or mister?
-Mister.
-Doctor mister?
-Mr. Mister.
-Mister misdemeanor.
-That's what you get when
you rob a Dairy Queen, right?
-Wow, she's pretty quick
with that cold steel.
-Nuts in her girdle.
-Good thing she has a handgun.
[Barking continues]
-Cujo?
-Hey, boy.
-Hey, come on.
This isn't funny.
-Guys? Guys?
-Don't take that off.
Your chin'll explode.
-Jackson, you been making
this noise out here?
Come on. Get down.
You know better than that.
[Jackson meowing]
-Oh, sorry, Jackson.
Was that your head?
-What is this doing out here?
-Just kind of lying there.
[Meowing continues]
-Oh, what a mess.
-A chocolate mess.
-That boy.
[Meowing continues]
He said he wasn't hungry,
and then he comes downstairs
and knocks these jars
off of the shelf.
-That proves he's hungry.
-...my jelly,
I'll tell you that.
-Oh, Helga, that tickles.
♪♪
-Hey, it's the title character.
-Cleaning after this kid...
-Mm-hmm.
-I recognize him.
He used to be with Def Leppard.
-Jackson, get away
from that ectoplasm.
-That boy.
Wait till I get
ahold of him tomorrow.
Why the shower curtain?
-That's a good question
for anyone.
♪♪
-Ooh, someone better callMadge, the Palmolive caseworker.
-Trying to wake me up
in the middle of the night,
as if I haven't
had enough of it.
Empty.
-Goodnight, sweet troll.
-She needs about 150 hours
of beauty sleep.
♪♪
-Aah, aah, aah!
-Aah!
-Oh, no.
Look out!
[All exhale in relief]
-They got us on that one.
-I knew it was coming.
-Can't believe she's got to do
that scene over again.
♪♪
Back in the kitchen.
-She forgot to put her
chin hammock on.
-Hey, what's that stuff?
-It's the nighttime coughing,
aching,
sneezing, stuffy-head, fever,
so you're being chased
by a human hand medicine.
♪♪
-Good.
-You know things are bad
when you keep a liquor cabinet
in your bedroom.
-That ought to do it.
-For a horse.
♪♪
-Oh, Helga. Oh, stewardesses.
Me, you, chandelier swinging.
♪♪
-I can't believe she's going to
do this scene one more time.
They used to call her One-Take
Sally, and now look, nothing.
-Let's see.
If I look at the dictionary,
I think
that's where I keep my stash.
♪♪
-Oh, I've seen this.
This is when she does her
Judy Garland impression.
-[Gagging]
-What the?
-Oh.
-No, I think she's doing
Mrs. Captain Kirk.
-Got to find push button.
-Must lay down.
Must perform death scene.
-Oh, grab your pills.
That'll help.
♪♪
-Helga?
-Mrs. Hotchkiss?
♪♪
Mrs. Hotchkiss?
-She's a victim
of a Hotchkiss disease.
-I bet he's going to be all
choked up now that she's dead.
All choked up,
get it, 'cause --
-Mm-hmm.
-And now a really big hand
for the little lady,
Mrs. Hotchkiss,
right here on our very floor.
-Hmm, rings, fingernails,
clippers,
Lubriderm lotion, it can't be.
No.
♪♪
It's a clue.
-Hey, little hand, little hand.
♪♪
-A big old booger.
-This goes in the jar
with the others.
-Ew.
-Operator, give me
the sheriff quick.
-If he's not there,
I'll talk to the skipper.
[Telephone ringing]
[Electric razor buzzing]
-♪ Shaving, shaving
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na
-Who?
Paul?
Paul Lawrence?
Will you stop talking so fast?
I can't understand
a word you're saying.
-[Panting] Dead, found her,
gunshot, and...
-Hotchkiss.
-Yes, Mrs. Hotchkiss.
-Now, don't touch anything.
-I won't. Just come.
-I'll be there in five minutes.
-Oh, hurry up. Oh, please.
-Now, look, Paul.
I know how you feel, son.
-No, you don't.
-I'll get there as fast
as I can.
-He doesn't know how he feels.
He's never been attacked
by a hand.
He has no idea how he feels.
Look at that boy.
He's got a ball of pain inside.
-Try and raise the countycoroner, Earl, and call my wife.
Tell her I'm liable
to up all night.
-Oh, we'd better
get out of here.
-I'll call his wife.
-Sure thing.
-I'll tell her she's married
to a two-bit character actor.
♪♪
-[Grunting] Got to think.
Must get back to Galileo Seven.
Lives of 400 crew members
hang in balance.
Aah!
-Vision fading.
Must --Must cut transponder from wrist.
Fashion crude phaser device
with bed slat and lightbulb.
-Must control myself.
Must find pastel-colored
native female.
Execute prime directive -- oh!
-[Grunting]
Hands so young-looking.
Mrs. Berg,
I thought you were dead!
Oh, oh, oh!
-Throat scratchy.
Hands so dry,
can scratch name into it.
-Embarrassing cuticles
on fingernails.
Must utilize emotional memory
and get to...
-Listen, Servo, stop it.
Stop it.
-Stop?
-No, unh-unh.
-That was my big scene, Joel.
-Hey, yeah, we were
just getting into it.
-This just isn't working.
I don't know how Shatner
does it week after week.
-I don't know why he does it
or who lets him do it.
-I think we should just be glad
he does it.
[Alarm buzzing]
-Oh, we've got movie sign.
Let's go!
-Must get to theater.
♪♪
-That hand thing killed me.
It was hilarious.
-Yeah.
-Pretty funny.
-We have to play
more games like that.
I like role-playing games.
[Dog barking in distance]
-You know, this book
of lists has everything.
Lookit here -- What to do when arogue hand kills your landlady.
-Hmm.
-Roddy McDowall,
Milton Berle, huh?
-[High-pitched] Hello? Hello?
-Operator, I would like to make
a long-distance call, please.
-I'll do what I can,
but I can't promise anything.
You know how things are.
You know, we've really got to
wait till the light comes on andthen...
-Sheriff.
-Skipper!
Where's the little body,
little buddy?
-I-I heard a shot.
I ran down from my room,
and I found her like this.
-No signs of a bullet.
Did you hear anything else,
like a door closing
or somebody running?
-Or the sound of
one hand clapping?
-No, nothing.
-Looks like she's
been strangled.
You can see the marks
on her throat.
No doubt about it.
-Hmm.
-Hmm, this lamp
has panties on it.
-Now, tell me, boy.
Did you ever see
this gun before?
-It belongs to Mr. Hotchkiss.
She told me
that it had a hair trigger.
-Smells like a hair trigger.
-Yes.
It probably fired
when it fell off the table.
Now, I know this hard
on you, boy,
but anything you can remember
will help, anything at all.
Now, do you recall,
did she leave any valuables
around the house,
any sizable amounts of money?
-Nothing that I found rifling
through her stuff.
-Not that I know.
-Well, that isn't
the way rumor has it.
That is, if you can believe
my wife, Edith,
and you can't always do that.
-So then rumor
wouldn't have it.
-That'll probably be Earl.
-I'll -- I'll get the door.
-Wow.
Psychic.
[All meowing]
-[Purrs]
[All yowling]
-That should do the trick.
At least that's what my wife,
Edith, says.
It usually does for her.
Two of those and a glass
of warm milk,
and she's out like a light.
-Make sure you drink
it like a raccoon.
-We'll go over the routine
questions in the morning.
Now, Paul, just one other thing.
Maybe you don't want to
stay here in the house.
I could drive you over
to my house,
and we'll find you
another place tomorrow.
-I've got a couple of hammocks
and a sailor's hat
I'd like you to wear.
-No, I'll be all right.
Don't worry about it.
-Soap and water will take
that ink off.
You better go upstairs
and try and get some sleep.
-Strange kid, dipping his hands
in ink like that.
How do you figure?
-All through downstairs, then.
-Think you got anything?
-Well, most of the prints
were pretty small.
They seemed to match the ones
that we got off
the gun and flashlight.
-Prince is pretty small.
-Yeah.
I think so,
but I can't tell you.
Oh, there was one that might be
interesting,
got it off the medallion
she was wearing.
-How soon can we get a report?
-Well, I'll telephoto a set
of these to Washington
and run a make on them here.
We ought to know something in,
oh, five or six hours.
What about the kid?
-Earl, I don't know.
I don't like to guess
on a case like this.
I just don't understand why
he wants to stay in the house.
I should think he'd want
to get as far away
from here as possible.
-Ah, he's a medical student.
He's used to being
around dead bodies.
-I suppose.
-Just like us.
-Now, come on.
We got a full night's work
ahead of us.
-Yeah, maybe if we're lucky,we'll get an hour of sleep, huh?
-Yeah, nice improv, ha-ha.
-Coconut cream pie,
just doesn't figure.
That cat is thirsty.
-His pants shrunk.
-Now, to catch a hand,
you've got to think like a hand.
I'll lay out
some press-on nails.
Yeah, that would work,
or maybe some lotion,
Lubriderm or...
Yeah, I know,
some Isotoner gloves.
That would work great.
-Oh, magic lamp,
help me find the hand.
-Dr. Weitzberg.
Weitzberg, Weitzberg.
[Rotary telephone spinning]
-[High-pitched]
Hello? Operator, hello?
-Operator,
long distance, please.
-Long distance to where?Where would you like to call to?
-I'd like to call...
-Spit it out.
-...a Dr. Max Weitzberg...
-Weitzberg,
how would you spell that?
-...in Washington D.C.
-Washington D.C.
-No, no, operator.
I-I don't have the number.
-Can you spell the name?
-This is an emergency.
-Is it an emergency?
-No, no. I'll hold on, okay?
-Could you hold on?
-Uh.
-How do you spell that name?
-No, uh, Weitzberg.
-Weitzberg? Weitzberg?
-W...
-...E...
-W, E.
-...I, T, Z...
-...I, T, Z, got you.
-...B...
-Keep trucking.
-...E...
-I can hear you,
but you're fading.
Are you on drugs?
Would you like
to call the drug hotline?
-No, G.
-Are you tripping?
-B, E.
-Uh, be on the lookout
for a crawling hand,
crawls up on the banister
and then drops on people.
Are you sure you can
hold on the line?
♪♪
I can't hear you.
Uh, are you -- Uh, uh.
It tends to drop on people rightwhen they are about to pass out.
Hello?
-Oh, geez!
-Wow!
This is action packed.
-Come on. Spit it out.
Cough it up.
[Siren wailing]
♪♪
-Uh, first word, uh,
sounds like, uh, smoke.
♪♪
-Coochy, coochy, coochy,
coochy, coochy, coo.
-Play-Doh face, Play-Doh face.
-Coochy, coochy, coochy.
-Did he just give him
a wet willy?
-I think he did.
With his own saliva.
Pretty tricky.
-Well, I sure could use a beer.
-Who couldn't?
-Mm-hmm.
-But we can't stop now.
-Bet there's some
in the kitchen.
-Not me, not here.
-Me neither.
-I'm looking for
a nice, cool beer.
-Uh-huh, a big tall,
frosty one.
-...hundreds of miles
away by now.
-Just think of that long, tall,
foamy brew.
-Yowza!
-Boy, you can talk a snake
out of his skin.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Okay, take a look.
With my luck,
she won't even have any.
-Dames like her
always keep beer around.
-Always.
-I told you there would be beer
in the refrigerator.
-Holy -- Come here!
-What's the matter?
-It's a two-for-one special.
-I don't know,
but I'm getting out of here.
-It's a body, dummy.
-Wait a minute.
It might still be alive.
-No, that's not a dummy.
That's a body.
-Listen, buddy, we were supposedto collect the dame
and that's all.
This guy is on his own.
-He is alive.
Let's get him out of here.
-You know, it doesn't get
any better than this.
[Siren wailing]
You spend a hard day
loading bodies, and you've got
one more than you bargained for.
It's Miller time.
W-W-What?
I was making
a long-distance call
and then all I remember is...
I slept with that?
-Wow, he really must of had
his beer goggles on.
-[Screaming]
[Tires screech]
-Oh, he's high.
-There goes the deposit.
-This happens every time
you work with a live one.
-Of course I don't believe it.
Who could?
And don't think I'm going to letsome fantastic story
about a ghost,fingerprints or no fingerprints,
stop me from carrying
out this project.
-Oh, now, wait a minute.
-I'm not waiting for anything.
-Calm down, Bucky.
-I was given a goal
and a time limit,
and the time limit
has just about run out.
-Lee, I think we're forgetting
the facts of the situation.
I know it all may sound
rather trivial
with all of your problems here,
but the fact of the matter
remains that a murder
has been committed,
and the prime suspect
in this case
happens to be one of our men.
-This was no suicide.
It was murder.
-I gather from the attitude
of Mr. Meidel of security
that it won't be long
before he applied
real pressure right here.
We may find ourselves right in
the middle of an investigation.
-However, you do have
an alternative, Lee.
When Meidel calls, you can gain
time by simply stating
that Lockhart had
no authorization
to be in California,
and at the present time,
you haven't the slightest idea
where he is.
An absolutely true statement,
one which you can't
possibly be criticized for.
-Unless you flub your lines.
-Steve and I could fly to Palms
and investigate
this ghost story.
It may hold up the project
a couple of days,
practically nothing to lose.
-Now what do you say?
-"It's tempting."
[Phone ringing]
-Alright. You win.
Go on. Take off.
-"Ha-ha! Now we can go work
on those o-rings."
-Barrenger speaking.
-"Hello, there. Are you wearing
rubber underwear?"
-Yes, Mr. Meidel.
[Engine roars]
-"Bye."
-"Got to think, must think.Must find hand. Must comb hair."
"Must get Vitalis, rub into
scalp, get rid of flaking."
-Paul?
-"Little buddy."
-Sheriff.
-Are you alright?
-Sure.
-Where have you been?
-"Out by the lagoon."
-I just took a walk.
I woke up.
I guess this thing bothered me
a little more than I thought.
I-I just took a walk.
-But you're filthy dirty.
-"Yeah, and you're
stocky tubby."
-You're all sweaty.
You must have walked
awfully hard.
Now, look, Paul.
I'm here because an ambulance
driver called me.
He told me a strange
kind of a story.
Have you got anything
to tell me?
-"Just a strange kind
of a story."
-No, sir.
-Alright.
Well, I'll tell you
what I want you to do.
I want you to stick close
to the house.
Now, I wouldn't go out at all
if I were you.
I don't care what you do,
but stick close to the house.
Do you understand?
-Oh, why don't you just go
ahead and arrest me
and get it over with?
-There's no charge
against you, boy, not yet.
-"I'm not a boy. I'm a man."
-I suggest that you go up
and get some sleep.
You've had a hard night.
-"Hard day's night."
-"D'oh!"
-"Hi, welcome to your room."
-"He's a rebel without a hand."
[Thuds, shuts drawer]
[Bed squeaks]
[Engine starts in distance]
[Engine revs, departs]
-"Dear Kitty, by the time
you hear this, I'll be dead."
-"Good morning, Mr. Phelps."
-I'm telling this really
for you,
Professor Farnstrom and Marta.
-"I would now like to sing
'Cathy's Clown.'"
-I know that you will both
realize that it is the truth...
-"I have touched
the unclean thing."
-...that I am not
out of my mind.
♪♪
You were right, Professor.
-"Dogs canfly.
Cold fusion isimpossible."
-...keep things to myself.
♪♪
I-I-I tried to be
a lone wolf and...
-"Now, I'm a dead dog."
-...I guess I wanted
all the credit for myself.
Marta and I were swimming,
and up on the sand,
we found something
quite interesting.
It was an arm...
-"Rocks."
-...just an arm.
It had a strange covering.
I-I-I guess
right away it must have been...
-"Tripping."
"Remind me not to
drop acid after school."
♪♪
-"He's doing his
Pete Townshend impression."
"There it is."
"People try to put us down."
-"That's the close-and-play
phonograph."
-"Drop it, stops."
-"Close it."
-"Shatters."
-"Step on it."
-"Smashes."
♪♪
-"Hey, it's Timothy Hutton."
-"No, it looks more like
an Adam Ant to me."
-"Oh, maybe."
-"It's from a place called
'Uncharted Desert Isle,' huh."
-"Dear Skipper,
why haven't you sent help?"
"Signed, the Castaways."
-When did this thing
arrive, Earl?
-Why?
What is it?
-It's from Washington.
We asked for a confirmation
on those fingerprints
at the Hotchkiss house.
Well, they say they belong
to a guy
I've never heard of, Lockhart.
-Who?
-"June's boy?"
-Melvin Lockhart.
Do you know a Melvin Lockhart?
-"June's boy?"
-Anybody in this town
with that name?
-Never heard of one.
-"June's boy?"
-That wasn't the half of it.
They're moving in.
-Who's moving in?
-"June's boy."
-Washington.
-"George?
Grover?"
-Great Caesar's ghost.
-"Julius, Augustus?"
-You tell me why they want in
on a case like this?
-"Curiosity, money?"
-Widow lady gets herself
killed, a prime suspect,
the only possible suspectI've got right here in my hands.
-"Boo."
-I was going to make an arrest
within a couple hours.
-Kid?
-Most certainly the kid.
You know the way
he's been acting.
-"Like us, bad."
-He's the only one that could
have possibly have done it.
Now they come up
with a man named Lockhart...
-"June's boy."
-...and they're taking over.
Earl, I'll tell you
what's happened.
They've got so many fingerprintsin Washington,
they've got them all mixed up.
-"[Chuckles]"
-Well, what's the use?
We can't buck them.
Not yet.
-"What?"
-"[Clears throat]"
-"[Whistles]"
-They also want to have us
put a guard on the house.
Nobody gets in.
-Want me to go over
and sit on the place?
-Yeah, you better.
-"Ought to bring a cushion."
-While you're there,
keep an eye on young Lawrence.
I suppose I should have
picked him up long before this,
but I just didn't want him
to have a record
until I was 100 percent sure.
-"He's such a sweet kid."
-And then after those
Washington boys
get through fooling around,
I'm afraid he's still
going to be it,
and I'd bet $100 on him.
-Okay.
I'll get right over there.
-Alright.
-"Damn Mary Anne."
♪♪
-"Clearasil.
Clearasil."
"Oxy. Oxy."
-Yes, what can I do for you?
-Afternoon, Sheriff.
I'm Steve Curan.
This is Doc Weitzberg,
and we're from Washington D.C.
-"We talk real fast."
-Well, you government boys
really work fast.
Got here in a hurry.
Let me get you some coffee.
-Well, thank you, no.
-Yeah, no thanks.
-So tell me.
Who is this man Lockhart?
-Wait a minute.
Let's not get started offon the wrong foot here, Sheriff.
-Yeah, I know.
You ask the questions, I don't.
-"Huh?"
-Well, you boys are from
the Bureau aren't you?
-Well, that's just it, Sheriff.
We're from Space Operations.
-Spa-Space Operations?
Oh, no.
Wait a minute, boys.
This is Palms, California.
Population 2,306.
-"We don't have space here."
-A woman gets
knocked off and...
-We know all about that,
Sheriff.
We just want to ask you
a few questions is all.
-About this very man Lockhart.
Has he been seen?
-Well, now I don't know
who you boys are
or why you're here.
As far as I'm concerned,
you've got no authority
at all to ask me questions.
-Now wait a minute.
We didn't come out here
to get pushed around.
-Now, Steve, just a minute.
Sheriff, as a matter of fact,
all we want is your permission
to go through the house.
-Nobody goes through the house.
Not until the boys
from the Bureau get here.
And I've got an armed guard
that says nobody does.
-"Yowza."
-"Oh, yeah, well,
we know Buzz Aldrin."
-"Fatty."
-Oh. Oh, uh, ah.
Oh, it's not so bad.
I don't really have acne anyway.I can go to that dance.
It's not a pimple.
It's my nose. [Chuckles]
What was I thinking of?
-"Hubcap. Duck."
-"Oh, okay."
-Oh, uh, we just talked
to the Sheriff.
-Yeah, he called me.
-Didn't change his mind,
did he?
-Nope.
-Well, uh, do you mind
if we just look around outside?
-Nothing to see,
but help yourself.
-Do you have any theories?
-Yeah, somebody killed her.
That's my theory.
-"Huh?"
-"Norman, get away
from the window, Norman."
-Well, Steve, I guess we might
as well be on our way.
-Hey, Doc.
You notice they don't
build houses like this anymore.
-"Kick sheriff.
Kick him."
-Oh, no they sure don't,
do they?
-No, they don't make houses
like this anymore.
Huh?
-Well, we'll see you
around, huh?
-See you later.
-Yeah.
-"Goodbye."
[Car starts]
[Engine revs]
-"Uh, your muffler."
-"Rapunzel, Rapunzel,
let down your hand."
-"I think they're going to do
a scene from 'Cyrano.'"
[Closes door quietly]
[Bird chirps]
-Whatever we've got to get
done, we better get done fast.
That cold fish could be
around here any second.
-"Hey, I think somebody just
called me a cold fish."
-"Why?"
-Did you distinguish whether
it was a man or a woman?
-No, it was a pretty
quick glance, Doc.
I'm not sure.
-Look, Steve.
-Huh?
-"Incoming! Duck!"
[Crack!]
-"Oh."
-Huh.
Well, the gate is over here.
Gate is over...
Hey, how did you get over there?
Uh, oh, geez, oh.
It's down there.
Could you get that for me?
-It's a note.
-"Come back tonight after dark.
The back door will be unlocked.
I have something important
to tell you."
-"Wear something sheer."
-No signature.
-Well, I didn't have
a date tonight.
Did you?
-Well, looks like we both
have now, isn't it?
-Hmm.
Let's see.
Something sheer.
How about that pink
chiffon number?
Oh, no, wait.
You're using that.
What about that taffeta,
that tea length?
You know, the one I wore
to the IGY convention?
You know, the night
I went home with Yuri Gagarin?
You remember.
[Car door closes,
engine starts]
-Hey.
-Hey!
-Hey, wait a minute.
Stop or I'll say, "Hey" again.
-"Ouch."
-"Do, do."
[Door latch clicks]
-Paul?
-"How'd she get in?"
-"She found the hole
in the security curtain."
[Footsteps]
-"Oh?"
-Paul.
-What are you doing here?
Get out.
-Well, are you alright?
I read in the paper
about poor Mrs. Hotchkiss.
Such a terrible thing.
-Never mind.
Get out of here.
-Well, that thing on the beach.
Just can't get it
out of my mind.
-Well, I can't get it
out of my house.
-...think about it?
-No.
Get out.
-Why are you staying here?
It's no good.
You can come to our house.
-Marta, please.
-Marta, what are
you doing here?
-"Yeah."
-Harrison, get her out of this
house. Just get her out!
-You just get back
to your room.
-No playing with your hand
and no supper.
-Wait a minute.
I have a right to see Paul.
I'm a friend of his.
-Get her out of this house!
-"I think he wants her
out of the house."
-Come on, Marta.
Come on.
-"Bye, Marta."
-And don't let her come back!
-"You think he's been watching
James Dean movies, you guys?"
-"Ohh!"
-"And what is that?"
"An ice cream place or..."
-"A coffeehouse, I think."
-"Bagel shop."
-"Pizza place?"
-"Oh, it's a mortuary."
-"It's a mortuary."
-"Silly us."
-"Oh, why didn't they say?"
-"Is that a peace sign?"
-"Wow."
-"Hope."
-"Hope?"
-"I hope this movie
is over soon."
-I don't know if she had any
relatives back east at all.
I know she used to speak
of an uncle,
but he was in England
or someplace.
Where did you say
you were from again?
-Pennsylvania.
-New York.
-Well, he's from New York.
-And he's from Pennsylvania.
We heard about the tragedy
and flew out here.
-Oh, I see.
Well, um, here she is.
You can take a look if you like.Really looks very well.
Of course, we got the bodyquite soon after the, uh, crime.
There weren't any marks
except the ones on her throat.
-"And the ones we added."
-You know, sometimes in cases
like this...
-Yes.
-"We put turtlenecks on them."
-Looks very well, I think.
-"Uh-huh."
-Yes, Steve, yes.
-"Hmm?"
-What's he doing?
What is that thing?
-"It's a DustBuster."
-Wards off evil spirits.
-Oh, I see.
-There's absolutely no doubt.
Thanks very much.
We're satisfied.
-And you are absolutely right.
She looks very well.
-Which is more than I can say
for you, baldy.
♪♪
-Hey, come back.
Is that really a DustBuster?
♪♪
-[Quietly] Hello?
-"Hi."
-Hello?
-Anybody here?
-"Yeah, us.
We're here. Hi."
-Looks like we're alone.
-"At last."
-Where our little friend is.
-"He's right here."
-I think he was watching
alright.
-He'll be down any minute.
-"I'll be your little friend."
-"Oh, it's
the crawling bladder."
-Couldn't we turn on a light?
-"These guys are the greatest
comedy team
since Willie Aames
and Scott Baio."
-Got to keep this flashlight
away from the windows.
-Steve?
-What?
-Give me the light.
Put it on the gauge.
-Yeah.
-What do you see?
-Well, there's an indication.
-It's faint, but it's definite.
-This corn relish
is radioactive.
-Steve, keep it up here.
-Yeah.
♪♪
-Well, what's it read?
-This is very strange.
-Why's that?
-Well, there is a very strong
reading right here
on top of the shelf,
nothing above or below.
-Now that's ridiculous, Doc.
-No man could get up
on that shelf.
It would never hold him.
-"Just part of a man, maybe."
-Doesn't have to be a man.
-"Just a hunch."
-Lockhart's fingerprints.
Remember?
-Yeah.
-Perhaps we can trace the trail
back to where it come from.
-Keep the light on the gauge.
-"Hey, who are they trying to
fool with that stud finder?"
-Look, Steve!
-"Yeah, they haven't
found me yet. [Chuckles]"
"See, stud? Me."
-"Oh, brother."
-Steve.
It's on the ceiling.
-Now, Doc, what man
do you happen to know
that walks on a ceiling?
-"Lionel Richie."
[Clicks]
-Turn off the light.
♪♪
-Alright.
Let him move first.
-Hello. Hello.
Come on.
Say something.
-"Hey, if you can't say
anything nice,
just don't say anything at all."
-"It's an Elvis zombie."
-[As Elvis] "Thank you.
Thank you very much."
-"Oh, Priscilla, make me
a banana sandwich."
-"Check out those classic Elvis
karate moves there."
-"Like from 'Blue Hawaii.'"
-"Yep."
-"Ladies and gentlemen,
Elvis has left the kitchen."
"Goodnight, everybody."
-Back in the house.
Come on.
Back up.
-"They're in the house."
-What are you two
doing back here?
-Well, don't bother about us.
Go after that maniac.
-Well, now you
must have seen him.
He ran right past you.
-"The guy in the rhinestones."
-I don't know
what you're talking about.
Into the house.
I'll call the Sheriff.
-Look, officer,
you're wasting time.
Go after that man.
-Shut up and get back
into the house.
-But...
-Alright.
Doc, there's nothing
we can do about it right now.
-Into the house.
-Why, you lily-livered,
flea-bitten federal boys...
-"Neh."
♪♪
-"He's got
the eye of the beast."
-"You know, if he sings Maria
right now,
I'm going to lose it, you guys."-"No, he won't sing it."
"He's not even sporting
a dance belt."
"Or dancing a sport belt."
♪♪
-"No zombies. Not allowed.
No zombies."
♪♪
"No strangling. Not allowed."
-"No lights."
-"Music is cool though."
-"Boy, you get a zombie
on the business end of a mop,
and there's no telling
what's going to happen."
-♪ Bird, bird, bird
♪ Murder is the word
Word, word, word ♪
♪♪
♪ Murder is the word
♪ M-Murder is the word
Murder is the word ♪
♪ We got a new dance
and goes like this ♪
♪ Murder is the word
Word, word, word ♪
♪ Well, you shake Bub up at
the end of your hand ♪
-♪ Bird, bird, bird
-♪ It goes like this
♪ The kid who knows Hotchkiss
-♪ B-b-bird,
bird, bird, bird ♪
♪ B-b-bird,
-I said, No killing.
-♪ Bird, a bird,
bird, bird, bird ♪
♪ Bird, a bird,
♪♪
-Oh, it's that rat boy.
-I guess a double-scoop sundae
is out of the question now?
-Huh?
-"We got to get out of here."
[Chairs creak]
-"Wow."
[Warbling, hissing]
[Fire crackles, whirring]
[Gate thuds, locks]
[Whirring, slams]
-"You know, that hand
is not so tough."
"What's the worst thinghe's going to do to you anyway?"
"Pinch you?"
-"Yeah, and how does he know
how to go after you?"
"He's got no brain
and no leverage."
-"Hey, what are you guys
talking about?"
-"Oh, we're just mocking
this week's monster."
"I mean, what's a hand
going to do to you anyway?"
-"Well, there's a lot of things
a hand can do"
"if you stop to think about it."
"Like, if you're sleeping, itcomes up with these two fingers,
shoves them up your nose,
you suffocate."
"Stone dead."
-"I hardly think
that's possible."
-"Or he could use this finger
and come up behind somebody
and tap them."
"Whiplash. Dead."
-"Oh, yeah right. I bet."
-"Well, and who knows
what else?"
"It's like he could
do this thing. Like that."
"You look down
until you're bored to death
or something like that."
-"Yeah, right, Joel.
Tell me about it."
-"Or let's say he had
an accomplice hand,
who was his friend,
and they'd gang up on you
and give you an Indian
rub like that."
-"Oh, stop it."
-"Right, Joel, sure."
"Tell us about it."
-"I can't believe
you guys don't..."
"Then there is the cuff,
chuck, gnaw,
norr, grab, neck, flip."
-"Geez. Oh, yeah."
-"Right."
"I don't think that hand
could scare me anyway."
"Free roaming, rogue,
disconnected, gloved."
"Even if it were connected to aforearm, it wouldn't bother me."
[Hissing]
"Tickle you to death? Sure."
"But scary? Ha!"
"Yeah, I knew a hand withcalluses the size of a football,
but it didn't scare me
in the least."
"Joel, remember that...
Joel?"
"Aah! Oh, oh, oh!"
♪♪
-I know I'll never
remember this stuff.
Nixon, O'Neill. [Sighs]
-"Joel, Joel, it was horrible."
"There's this big hand
chasing me."
-Don't you understand it,
Marta?
-"We got him.
Oh, we were teasing you."
"That was Gypsy
in a giant hand costume."
-"We scammed you."
-"What?"
-"Yeah."
-"Oh, I-I knew that, yeah."
-"Watch the movie."
-That exam is tomorrow,
and you've got to pass.
You know they expect twice
as much from foreign students.
-"You know the boys do."
-Oh, I wasn't listening.
Just that...
-I know you're concerned
about Paul.
Oh, but he'll be okay.
-Oh, Patsy.
I just don't understand it.
What's happened to him?
It is terrible.
-"Well, it's time
she explained puberty to you."
-Why is he staying
in that house?
-Gee, I don't know.
Pop hasn't said a word
about it at home.
There's no use me asking him.
He just won't tell me anything
about stuff like that.
-They're keeping him
a prisoner.
-Well, he may be a suspect.
-Paul didn't kill anyone.
-"He's Paul."
-That I'm sure of.
-Pop always says
you can't be sure
what anyone is going to do
in certain circumstances.
-"Yeah, but your was
in 'Gilligan's Island.'"
-He didn't kill anyone.
I'm sure of that.
-"Oh, he may choke the heck
out of people at times,
but kill, naw."
-I thought it's perhaps time
for a little rest
and refreshment.
You know studying at such fiercepace without pause
can be very exhausting.
-I'm afraid that's not the case.-"Grandpa Ed."
-Not with me.
-No?
-In any case,
sandwiches and Coke,
and I've made quite
a tempting little snack.
-Oh, you sold me, Professor.
Lead the way.
-Don't you want some?
-"You mention hors d'oeuvres,
and the babes go wild."
-I'm really not hungry.
-"It's alright.
I'm really not your grandpa."
-...studying,
and I better start,
I'm afraid, if I don't want
to flunk tomorrow.
-Oh, well, as you wish.
Patsy and I will have to eat
extra portions then.
-"Yeah, and Patsy can really
tuck away the chow."
-Be back in a few minutes, pal.
[Door thuds]
-"Wow, look.
She really is smart."
[Ominous music plays]
-"Hey, that looks like
Roland Gift
from 'Fine Young Cannibals.'"
-[As Roland Gift] Hi.
I'm Roland Gift from the
"Fine Young Cannibals."
[Rapid tapping]
♪♪
You drive me crazy.
[Window latch rattles]
-Paul!
-Could I talk to you
for a minute?
-Yes, of course.
Come inside.
-It's about your stairs.
There are none.
-I've been so worried.
-I know.
Listen.
I'm going away.
-Away?
When?
-Away. You know, not here.
-Now, just as soon
as I get rid of something
that must be destroyed.
-"His plantar warts?"
-I just couldn't go without
saying goodbye first.
-Paul, what's the matter?
What are you afraid of?
Tell me.
-"The Dark?
Well, no, not the dark."
-I can't.
Just something
I want to tell you.
I didn't kill Mrs. Hotchkiss.
-Oh, I know that, Paul.
You couldn't have.
-There are people
who think I did.
Sheriff Townsend.
-"Pete Townsend.
John Entwistle.
The list goes on."
-But you didn't.
Everything will be alright.
-"He looks like Bob Crane."
-Your grandfather will...
-"Hogan!"
-He loves you very much, Paul.
-Don't touch me.
Listen.
I can't explain it,
but I'm all mixed up, and --
and there's something terrible
that's happened to me,
and I-I-I...and I-I...
There's only one person
that I could have relied on
in this world,
and I almost killed him
a few minutes ago.
-What do you mean?
-Never mind.
It would take too long
to explain.
I don't have the time...
-"Or the communication skills."
-There are times
when I'm alright,
and then I'm not,
and then I'm...
and then when I'm myself,
and I'm not,
and the periods when I'm myselfare getting shorter and shorter.
Do you understand?
-No.
-Well, then don't try!
-"Geez."
-"She doesn't understand much,
really.
She is very smart."
-No, Paul.
I'm not going to let you go.
If you're ill, we'll help you.
You can come and stay with us,
and we'll take care of you
until you're well.
-"I'm not moving in here until
you get some front stairs."
-Remember when you asked me
that question,
whether I was going back home
after the summer was over?
I was only teasing you.
I never meant to go.
I want to stay here.
I want to be here with you.
I love you, Paul.
-No, you don't understand.
-I won't.
I won't let you run away.
-No.
No.
Get away from me!
-"Joel, I smell a big
juicy transformation scene
coming up here."
-Paul, what's the matter
with you?
-"Yeah."
-"His neck is stiff,
for God's sake."
"Leave him alone."
-What is it?
What's the matter with you?
♪♪
[Shrieks]
-"Hey, it's Sid Vicious."
-"That was rotten, Johnny."
-"And she's Nancy."
"And that looks a lot
like the Chelsea Hotel."
-Marta!
-Huh?
-"He's the least successful
strangler in the movies."
"He runs around the countryside
giving people Dutch rubs."
[Marta gasping]
-"That's when a siren
was a siren."
[Siren wails]
"Headlights were headlights."
-"Hats were hats."
-Sheriff, we're sorry.
We should have listened to you.
We had no idea
the boy was so dangerous.
-"Heavies were heavy."
-You two should have thought
of that when
you helped him escape...
-"And sheep roamed
the countryside."
-...both of you.
-Be reasonable now.
-If he does any harm
to that Farnstrom girl,
I'll show you
how unreasonable I can be.
-"Then I'm going to whack you
with my sailor hat."
-My daughter's at
the Farnstrom place too.
[Siren continues]
[Tires screech]
-Whoa.
-"Just pull your hands away."
-Paul's face was white,
horrible.
[Siren approaching]
[Tires screech]
[Siren stops]
-Thirteen-thirteen
Mockingbird Lane.
This is the place, alright.
-Every time I get a boyfriend,
he crushes my windpipe.
I don't get it.
-[Breathing heavily]
-May I speak with her,
professor?
-Sure, skipper.
-In a moment.
-Marta, it was Paul Lawrence,
wasn't it?
-One long biscuit for yes.
Two for no.
-Paul?
Not really Paul.
-"Not Paul, but
an incredible simulation."
-It was in the sand.
It was an arm lying in the sand.
A human arm.
-"Just speak it."
-"Oh!"
-"Ooh."
-"Oh, no."
-"Ah!"
-"Ugh."
-"Oh, oh."
-"You drive me crazy."
[Somber music plays]
♪♪
-"A crawling torso."
-It was Paul Lawrence,
wasn't it?
-"Can't he ever use the stairs?"
[Cat yowls]
-"He's a welcome cat now."
♪♪
-"Poor screwed up kid."
-"Poor screwed up cat."
-"Hey, little hand,
where are you, buddy?"
"Oh, that's a dust bunny.
That's no good."
"There's a latex hand,
and I found my Carmex."
"There's some sand
in it though."
-"Let's see."
"If I were an arm,
where would I hide?"
"My sleeve, of course.
[Chuckles] No?"
"Maybe the meat freezer?"
"Yeah."
♪♪
-"Ooh?"
-"Cage match.
Arm wrestling."
-"His bag for the arm."
-"You're not going to wash that
with the whites, are you?"
♪♪
-"Quick! Throw him
in the trash compactor."
"Set it on mulch."
-"The quickest way to turn
a big hand into a little hand."
-"Nice hand off."
♪♪
-"Is he going to use that
to signal turns now?"
♪♪
-"Here comes the long arm
of the law."
-Hey!
His car is gone.
It was parked right there
at the curb.
-Put a call out on the car.
I'll make a double-check inside.
-Unit one to control.
-Hmm. Everything seems to be in
order in the old woman's room.
-Except there's
no old woman here.
-Well, you can't just
leave them lying around.
-Paul?
-George, or John, Ringo?
Who am I kidding? They'll never
get back together again.
[Door closes]
-Thirty-nine A.
Code seven.
-Spotted him heading down
a county dump road,
but he gave them the slip.
-You stick close to the house
just in case.
We'll check with you later.
-"This guy has the worst job,
just staying around the house
day after day,
night after night."
-One Adam 12.
See the appendage
corner of Druxter and Main.
Be advised.
He's arm and dangerous.
♪♪
[Siren wails]
-"Traveling in the woody."
-"Taking the world by storm."
[Tires squeal]
[Siren wailing]
"Oh, man. He's going to soil
that kid's stadium blanket."
[Siren wailing]
[Tires squealing]
-"Hey! Signal those turns."
-"That hand should
moisturize more."
"That could be eczema,
seborrhoea..."
[Siren wails]
"...psoriasis."
-♪ "Itsy-bitsy spider
went up the water spout" ♪
[Siren wails]
-"Boom."
♪ "Then came the rain
and washed the spider out" ♪
-"What's bugging
that hand anyway?"
-"It's got a personal vendetta
against anyone
with a full body."
-"You got to hand it
to him though."
-"Oh, you."
-"That limb's revolting."
♪♪
-"Hey!
I'm trying to drive."
-"See, now that's the kind of
thing I'm talking about."
"You can tell
it's a low-budget movie
because they can't
wreck the cars."
"See?"
-"Good point."
♪♪
"'The Crawling Hand.'"
"You will believe
a hand can crawl."
-"That's the Australian
crawl I think."
-"You will believe
Alan Hale can act."
-"No."
♪♪
-"Sleeveless."
-"This all sort of
a hand jive, isn't it?"
-"Yep.
I was born to hand jive."
♪♪
-"Oh, outflanked him."
-"What?"
-"That's got to hurt."
[Glass shatters]
♪♪
-"Ouch."
-"Oh, gee. Oh, oh, oh."
-"Hey, hand-to-hand combat."
♪♪
-"Yeah, now tell that
to the rest of your body."
[Cats yowl, hiss]
[Siren wailing]
♪♪
-"Here they come
to save the day."
-"The cops will handle it."
-"Get a grip on yourself, Crow."
-Thirty-nine A, clear.
♪♪
-What's this?
-Metallic cloth, it looks like.
-I've never seen anything
like that.
-"What, have you been stranded
on a desert isle?"
-Space travel.
-There's a prowler
at the rear door.
-Lockhart's.
I can bet my life.
-"You might have to."
♪♪
-I'll circle around this way.
-There he is.
-"And he's looking good."
♪♪
-Wait a minute. You're not goingto gun him down, are you?
-He's a killer.
If he doesn't come quietly,
I'll have to shoot him.
-But he's just a kid.
-Sure he's just a kid.
I know all about kids like him.
The county jail is full of them.
-"Sal Mineo impersonators?"
-Paul!
Paul, don't do anything foolish.
-That's right, Paul.
I don't want to hurt you.
Now put that bottle down,
and come over here quietly.
-"Put that bottle down."
-Come on now, boy.
I wouldn't want to use this gun.
Now, put the bottle down
so we can get back into town.
♪♪
Paul, listen to me.
You didn't hurt her.
-"Think, Paul, think!"
-Marta is alright.
[Hisses, yowls]
-"Catfight."
♪♪
-"Cats can't resist
the cosmic treat."
-"They're eating right
out of his hand."
-Paul.
-"The beefy, moist meal
in a sleeve."
-Come on now.
You going to put
that bottle down,
or am I going to have
to take it away from you?
♪♪
-"Think about it, Paul."-"They're living hand-to-mouth."
-"Not a lot of meat
on that hand,
but if you cook it right,
it's good eating."
-"I like buffalo
astronaut arms myself."
[Growling, hisses]
-"Who doesn't?"
♪♪
"It's amazing that
a disembodied hand
still bleeds with
no blood pressure or anything."
-"Mm, knuckle sandwich."
♪♪
-"Nice swoon."
-"Good form."
-"Came out of his tuck
and everything."
-We better get him to
a hospital right away. Come on.
-"This hand isn't
crawling anywhere."
-[Sighs]
-Hmm?
-[Gasps]
-Doc!
-Huh?
-Doc, come over here.
-Hey, don't leave me
with the kid.
-Oh, this was
no boating accident.
-Fingerprints don't lie.
[Sighing] Oh.
-I'm here, Steve.
-Thirty-four, clear.
-Okay, you two, let's go.
-Hey, what you looking
for, fatty?
-"[Groaning] Yeah."
-Not a trace,
not a solitary trace.
-"Must be a talent-meter."
-Not bad, Doc.
-There's my boy,
just hypertension now.
What you had is an entirely
different matter,
and we'll talk about it
when you get well.
-What I had,
what happened to it?
-Let's just say that life
can exist
under different temperatures,
and a fever of 104
was enough to finish it off,
fortunately for you and for us.
-I just talked to Barrenger.
He wants to see it immediately.
-Good.
-I'm glad he does.
The sooner we get rid of it,
the better.
-Oh, Marta, come on in.
-Is he alright?
-For a little while,
I think it'll do him
more good than harm.
Excuse me.
-"I think so too."
-Are you sure you got
that thing fixed
so it won't ever get away again?
-Don't worry about it, Sheriff.
It's in a metal box,
and it's locked,
and in about 2 minutes,it's going to be on an airplane,
and no one
will ever see it again.
-That'll be alright with me.
-"Unless the weather starts
getting rough."
-"Well, I'm on my way
for a 3-hour tour."
-Come on, tell me.
Did you mean what you said
last night about staying here?
-"Yes, I intend not to."
-I don't play games.
I'm too weak.
-How can I help myself?
You know women
can't resist weak men.
-Then you're going to stay?-"Or the rich taste of s'mores."
-Just you wait. Just wait until
I get out of his bed.
Just you wait.
-"Me and my extra arm."
[Chatter]
-"Oh, no.
Not these two guys."
-"Man, they couldn't even work
for Domino's Pizza delivery."
-"About time for a tall, cool
one, a couple of road sodas."
-I wonder what all the secrecy
is about this time.
-There you go,
sticking your nose into
something that's none
of your business.
All we're supposed to do
is deliver it to the airport.
-Yeah, but those people
inside got me curious.
You know that fella
from Washington,
the way he kept looking at it,
asking me if I was sure
it was locked...
-"Yeah?"
-...I'd give anything
to take a look inside.
-Not me.
I don't care what's in it.
Come on.
Let's get moving.
-That's your trouble:
no curiosity.
You'll never get anyplace
without curiosity.
You've got to find out
about things.
-Yeah?
Well, I like it that way.
-What harm will it do
to take a look?
I've got the key.
-It might be dangerous.
-[Chuckles] What, do you think
it's alive?
You don't see any holes
in the box.
You think it'll bite you
or something?
-"Way to go, Mr. Logic."
-You're always talking me
into doing something
I don't want to do.
-Have I ever steered you wrong?
-"Well, there's that whole
beer-dead-body thing, yeah."
-"No, don't do it, guys."
-"We better get out of here."
"Yeah, come on."
-"Don't do it."
-"Let's go, you guys."
-"Oh!"
-"Ah, I knew it'd be
something like that."
-"Next time, use Federal Expressor maybe hand delivery."
♪♪
-♪ About the bird
the bird ♪
♪ Bird, bird, bird
♪ Bird, the bird, bird, bird
[Warbling, hissing]
[Fire crackles, whirring]
[Gate thuds, locks]
[Whirring, slams]
-"Okay, you guys.
That's the end of the movie."
"We made it."
-"Yay."
-"And this is time
for the RAM chip episode
where you say a good thingabout the film and a bad thing."
"You get a RAM chip.
Okay?"
-"Yay."
-"Ready?"
"Go ahead, Crow."
-"Uh, well, let's see."
"The good thing was those cats
showed us
a new definition
for finger food."
"Finger, get it?"
-"Ah, and the bad...Yeah."
-"Yeah."
-"And the bad thing?"
-"Bad thing was, well,
never trust a delivery man."
-"Right. Okay.
Here is your RAM chip."
"There you go.
Alright?"
"Now, Tom Servo?"
-"Mm-kay."
"The good thing was there
was a Swedish babe in the film
who didn't get killed."
-"Yeah, and the bad thing?"
-"She didn't spend the time
on her makeup that it deserved
as the film went on."
-"Okay.
Here is your RAM chip, pal."
"Oh, there you go.
Alright."
"Well, we want to thankeverybody who's been writing in,
and I want to thank
the mad scientists
for faxing the letters
back up to me,
but anyway, this one isfrom Ricky Faus, and he says..."
"He wrote some letters,
and this one is to you, Crow."
-"Oh, hey.
Thanks, Ricky."
-"He goes, 'Dear Crow,
I really like you.
I laugh when you make a joke,'
so that's a good thing, right?"
-"Have I made one yet?"
-"Yeah."
"'And I hope I can
see you someday.'"
"Alright?"
-"Take a look, kid."
-"Yeah.
And, 'Joel, someday,
I would like you
to take apart Servo.'"
-"Oh, hey."
-"Yeah."
-"Hey, can I help?"
-"And 'I like Gypsy
because he looks cool.'"
"Gypsy is a she by the way,
and that's from Ricky Faus,
and he also did some drawings."
"We got those in still store,
don't we, Cambot?"
"Okay.
Let's take a look at that."
"We got one of Crow."
-"Whoa."
-"And then it says,
'Look on back,'
and you turn it around,
and we got a Tom Servo there."
-"Hey."
-"See, isn't that neat?"
-"Nice."
-"And then on the next one,
it says, Gypsy,
looks like this,
and then it says,
'Look on back,'
and it's got Joel right there."
"See, I got a little light bulb
above my head
because I had a bright idea."
-"It looks perfect too."
-"Yeah."
"Alright.
Well, read the address, Crow."
"Keep the cards and letters
coming in, everybody."
-"Can I do it?"
-"Servo, read it."
-"I'll do it."
-"Tom Servo,
read the letter there."
-"Okay."
-"Alright."
"Send your letters to the
Mystery Science Theater
Fan Club, P.O. Box5325, Hopkins, Minnesota, 55343.
Send them now."
-"Right."
-"Yay."
-"Thanks a lot for watching."
"Scientists,
I hope you're happy."
-"Yeah. Yeah. I'm happy.
Are you happy, Clay?"
-"Ow."
-"Huh? Huh?"
-"Ugh, yeah."
-"Huh, Clay?"
"Tell them. Are you happy?
Tell them."
-"I got to reach console,
got to end experiment."
-"Oh!"
[Pop!]
♪♪